{
    "id": "212b5216fc974c2e8fea87ff3954040d",
    "title": "Clauses worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "0c2cada2c5214043840c6904ab5eaf6b",
            "title": "Clauses Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Maria bought some flowers which she wanted to give her mother.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Adjective clause",
                        "Adverb clause",
                        "Noun clause"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t know the reason why she hates me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Adjective clause",
                        "Adverb clause",
                        "Noun clause"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He drove fast so that he might reach the airport in time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Adjective clause",
                        "Adverb clause",
                        "Noun clause"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The professor was speaking so softly that we could not hear him at all.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Adjective clause",
                        "Adverb clause",
                        "Noun clause"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The gardener said that all the plants had been pruned neatly.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Adjective clause",
                        "Adverb clause",
                        "Noun clause"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The angler said that he hadn’t caught any fish that morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Adjective clause",
                        "Adverb clause",
                        "Noun clause"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wondered if she was free.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Adjective clause",
                        "Adverb clause",
                        "Noun clause"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Though he didn’t receive formal schooling, he is clever and industrious.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Adjective clause",
                        "Adverb clause",
                        "Noun clause"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boys who misbehaved in the class were suspended.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Adjective clause",
                        "Adverb clause",
                        "Noun clause"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He who laughs last laughs best.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Adjective clause",
                        "Adverb clause",
                        "Noun clause"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}